http://www.netbabyworld.com/legal/privacy.html

PRIVACY POLICY
PLAYCOM GAME DESIGN ("PLAYCOM") HAS DEVELOPED ITS WEBSITE, WWW.NETBABYWORLD.COM, TO BE AN ENJOYABLE EXPERIENCE FOR ALL PEOPLE WITH ACCESS TO THE INTERNET, REGARDLESS OF AGE, GENDER OR NATIONALITY. WE RESPECT THE PRIVACY OF ALL OUR GUESTS AND THEREFORE WE AIM TO REQUIRE ONLY A MINIMUM OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. FURTHERMORE, NO NETBABYWORLD PRODUCT CONTAINS LETHAL VIOLENCE OR SEXUAL ELEMENTS.
YOU DO NOT HAVE TO REGISTER TO GET ACCESS TO THIS SITE OR TO PLAY OUR GAMES. MEANWHILE, WE WANT TO PRESENT ACTIVITIES ON NETBABYWORLD.COM THAT ARE TAILORED TO THE NEEDS OF OUR USERS. FOR THIS REASON WE ASK YOU TO REGISTER WHEN VISITING CERTAIN AREAS, OR THE NETBABYCLUB. TO GET REGISTERED AT THOSE AREAS YOU DO NOT HAVE TO FILL IN YOUR PERSONAL NAME, INSTEAD YOU ARE FREE TO CHOOSE AN ALIAS.
PLAYCOM ONLY COLLECTS PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM VISITORS ON A VOLUNTARY BASIS. GENERALLY, WE ONLY USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO CONTACT PEOPLE WHO COMMUNICATE WITH US DIRECTLY VIA E-MAIL (PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IS INFORMATION THAT CAN BE USED TO LOCATE AN INDIVIDUAL EITHER ONLINE OR OFFLINE). BY ALLOWING VISITORS TO SEND E-MAIL TO PLAYCOM WE ARE NOT ATTEMPTING TO COLLECT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, WE WILL USE SUCH INFORMATION ONLY TO RESPOND TO A SPECIFIC INQUIRY.
WE SOMETIMES COLLECT INFORMATION TO FIND OUT HOW PEOPLE EXPERIENCED THIS SITE, WHICH PAGES THEY VISITED, AND FOR HOW LONG THEY LOGGED ON. THIS INFORMATION WILL NOT INCLUDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION. WE JUST NEED TO FIND OUT ABOUT THESE THINGS, TO KEEP IMPROVING NETBABYWORLD.COM.
WHEN YOU REGISTER AT NETBABYWORLD.COM, WE MAY ALSO ASK FOR DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION, SUCH AS GENDER, HOME COUNTRY AND AGE. THIS INFORMATION WILL BE USED FOR INTERNAL DEMOGRAPHIC STUDIES ONLY, AND TO BETTER MEET THE NEEDS OF OUR VISITORS OR OTHERWISE IMPROVE THIS SITE. FOR EXAMPLE WE NEED SUCH INFORMATION TO CREATE OUR HI-SCORELIST, WHERE YOU CAN COMPARE HI-SCORES, BOTH WORLDWIDE AND NATIONALLY AS WELL AS IN TEAMS.
WHO WILL HAVE ACCESS TO THE INFORMATION?
WHEN PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE DATA IS SUBMITTED TO PLAYCOM, FOR EXAMPLE WHEN VISITORS SEND US E-MAIL OR REGISTER FOR NEWSLETTERS, PLAYCOM DOES NOT SELL OR OTHERWISE DISCLOSE THAT INFORMATION. IT IS USED SOLELY FOR INTERNAL PURPOSES.
HOWEVER, TO BETTER MEET THE NEEDS OF VISITORS FROM ALL OVER THE WORLD, PLAYCOM HAS LICENSE-HOLDERS IN DIFFERENT COUNTRIES. ON SOME OCCASIONS OUR LICENSE-HOLDERS WILL ADMINISTER INFORMATION ABOUT VISITORS FROM A SPECIFIC REGION. FOR EXAMPLE WHEN A VISITOR SENDS US E-MAIL A PLAYCOM LICENSE-HOLDER MAY HELP US RESPOND TO IT IN THE VISITOR'S FIRST LANGUAGE. OUR LICENSE-HOLDERS ONLY USE PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM A VISITOR ON A VOLUNTARY BASIS, SUCH AS TO RESPOND TO AN INQUIRY.
IF YOU REACH NETBABYWORLD.COM THROUGH A LARGER PORTAL AND YOU CHOOSE TO REGISTER, THAT PORTAL WILL ON SOME OCCASIONS HAVE ACCESS TO YOUR REGISTRATION. PLEASE READ THE PRIVACY POLICY OF THAT SPECIFIC PORTAL CAREFULLY TO MAKE SURE IT RESPONDS TO YOUR PRIVACY AND SECURITY CONCERNS. PLAYCOM HAS NO CONTROL OVER THE PRIVACY POLICIES OR OTHER ASPECTS OF THESE WEBSITES.
REVIEW, CORRECTION & DELETION
IF YOU LOG ON AND REGISTRATE AT NETBABYWORLD.COM YOU ARE ABLE TO REVIEW AND CHANGE YOUR REGISTRATION AT ANY TIME. IF, FOR ANY REASON, YOU WISH TO HAVE YOUR NAME REMOVED FROM OUR RECORD, PLEASE CONTACT US AT INFO@NETBABYWORLD.COM (SEE BELOW FOR REGULAR MAIL ADDRESS, PHONE OR FAX). WE WILL BE HAPPY TO UPDATE OR DELETE INFORMATION AS APPROPRIATE.
NEWSLETTER
IF YOU SIGN UP FOR OUR NEWSLETTER, EACH TIME THE NEWSLETTER IS E-MAILED YOU CAN UNSUBSCRIBE YOURSELF FROM THE MAILING LIST BY REPLYING TO IT AND ENTERING "REMOVE" WITH YOUR E-MAIL ADDRESS IN THE SUBJECT LINE.
USE OF COOKIES
COOKIES ARE PIECES OF INFORMATION DOWNLOADED TO YOUR COMPUTER WHEN VISITING A WEBSITE. A COOKIE IS LIKE A DIGITAL FOOTPRINT, CONTAINING CERTAIN INFORMATION THAT TELLS US THAT YOU HAVE VISITED THIS SITE BEFORE AND HELPS US TRACK MOVEMENTS WITHIN OUR SITE. THESE STATISTICS WILL NOT INCLUDE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. WE CAN NOT TELL WHO YOU ARE OR WHERE YOU ARE.
NETBABYWORLD USES COOKIES PRIMARILY TO MAKE YOUR VISIT AT THIS SITE MORE ENJOYABLE. WE MAY ALSO USE THE COOKIE TO SURVEY THE NUMBER OF VISITORS TO OUR SITE. WHEN TRACKING USER TRAFFIC PATTERNS, PLAYCOM WILL ONLY USE THE INFORMATION TO CALCULATE THE TOTAL NUMBER OF PEOPLE VISITING OUR WEB SITE, AND IN A NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE FORM.
MOST MAJOR WEBSITES USE COOKIES FOR THE ABOVE-MENTIONED PURPOSES. YOU CAN DISABLE COOKIES OR SET YOUR BROWSER TO INFORM YOU WHEN COOKIES ARE BEING SENT. IF YOU DO SO, PLEASE NOTE THAT SOME AREAS OF OUR WEBSITE WILL NOT FUNCTION.
AGREEMENT
THIS DOCUMENT SUPERSEDES ANY PRIOR COMMUNICATION ON THIS TOPIC AND REFLECTS OUR ENTIRE AND EXCLUSIVE PRIVACY POLICY FOR THIS WEBSITE. BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU HAVE AGREED TO THIS POLICY.
QUESTIONS?
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY OR REGARDING
NETBABYWORLD, PLEASE FEEL FREE TO CONTACT US VIA E-MAIL: contact@playcom.se,
REGULAR MAIL: PLAYCOM GAME DESIGN AB, VIDEHUSET I PARTIHALLARNA, SE-400 13 GOTHENBURG, SWEDEN
FAX: +46 31 707 88 41. FROM THE US, PLEASE FAX: 1-413-826-3789.
CREATED 2001/05/21, ©1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002, 2003 PlayCom Game Design AB
Contact Us | Press | Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2003 PlayCom Game Design AB All rights reserved.
